http://www.capable.nl/privacy-statement

Cookies and Privacy Statement
You are visiting a website owned and operated by Capable BV. In using the website owned and operated by Capable BV (the “Website”) the latter and/or third parties such as social networks (Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google +) may collect information about your use of this and other websites, through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small file downloaded onto your computer when you access pages of a website and it’s stored by your browser on your computer’s hard-drive. The cookie enables your browser to be identified during repeated visits to a website. The information collected by Capable BV and/or third parties through the use of cookies, can be used for analytical purposes.
Capable BV furthermore uses the service of Google Analytics (the US-based company Google that sets cookies on websites as part of its Analytics service) in order to track, and receive reports on, how people use the website.  Google may share this information with third parties if it is required to do so by law, or if third parties process the data on behalf of Google. Note that this process is beyond Capable BV's control.
The data relating to your device and browser which Capable BV collects on the Website are the following:
• Your device’s IP address (this is stored on an anonymized basis);
•  The type of device used and your browser.
The data relating to your visit which Capable BV collects on the Website are the following:
• The website through which you found our website;
• The pages you visited;
• The country in which you are located at the time you visit our website;
• The date and time of your visit to our website.
Deleting and rejecting cookies
You can use your computer’s browser settings to delete previously stored cookies and prevent new cookies from being stored. The method used for storing cookies depends on the type of browser; you can use your browser’s help function if necessary. Rejecting and/or deleting cookies only has an effect on the computer and the browser on which you perform this act. If you are using multiple computers and/or browsers, you must repeat the act(s) described above as often as necessary.
Privacy Statement
By using the Website you leave certain information behind. This could be personal data: data that could be traced back to you. We only keep and use the personal data that is submitted directly by you or for which is clear that it has been submitted for processing purposes.
The personal data processed by Capable BV, if applicable, based on the cookies set, is subject to the Capable BV Privacy Statement. Capable processes your personal data as permitted by and in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations such as the Dutch Data Protection Act (“Wet Bescherming Persoonsgegevens”) and the General Data Protection Regulation as soon as it becomes effective (25 May 2018).
Security
Capable BV has taken technical and organisational security measures. All data that you provide us via the Website is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Capable takes measures to continuously and carefully protect the data it collects against loss, unauthorized disclosure and unlawful processing, Capable constantly seeks to improve and update the measures applied. Capable has an internal procedure for handling data leaks.
Contact us
Do you have any questions or do you want to start your own project?
Please contact our sales and engineering team by e-mail or phone
of applications in high-tech environments.
Let's talk
Follow us on LinkedIn
Privacy Statement
Capable is part of the CCG Group
